再来杯咖啡
Can I have another?
麻烦 再来杯咖啡
Hey. Can I have some more coffee, please?
别走啊
Where you going?
劳驾
Excuse me.
泼妇
Bitch.
有人吗
Hello?
Anyone here?
小姐
Lady. Lady.
有人吗
Hello?
搞什么
What the fuck?
阿斌
Dean. Dean.
若你再睡下去 会被赶出去
I told you, if you keep falling asleep, they're gonna kick you out of here.
对不起 下次不敢
Um, sorry. Won't happen again, okay?
好的
Okay.
- 南希 - 克莉丝 快坐
- Nancy. - Hey, Kris. You can sit wherever you want.
- 其实我是来找阿斌 - 他就在那
- Actually, I'm just here to meet Dean. - Oh, he's right over there.
谢谢
Thanks.
嗨
Hey.
你看起来好像…
Wow, you look like you haven't…
三日没睡过
Like I haven't slept in three days?
阿斌 发生什么事
Dean, what's going on?
接下来做什么
So, what are we doing after this?
看是否有可去的地方
Let me see if we can go to Ashley's or whatever.
我没什么主意
Then I don't know.
你女友来了
Look out, here comes your girlfriend.
- 嘿 - 还想要什么
- Oh, hey. - Hi. Can I get you guys anything else?
嗯 嗯
Uh… Um…
够了 我们准备埋单
No, I think we're good. We'll just get the check.
伟庭 你就只会跟她说这些
Is that the only thing you wanna ask her, Quentin?
蠢材
Asshole.
嗨
Hey.
克莉丝和阿斌在一起喔
Why is Kris with Dean?
好的
Okay.
走
Come on.
该死的
That's fucked up.
怎么了
What was that all about?
杰西还因和克莉丝分手而耿耿于怀
Um, Jesse's just… He's pissed because Kris broke up with him.
- 我不知道他们在一起过 - 嗯
- I didn't even know they were together. - Yeah.
找钱不要吧
I guess I can keep the change?
看…
Yeah. Look…
很抱歉桌面弄得如斯杂乱
…I'm sorry about the mess.
- 他们只是… - 我习惯了
- These guys are just… - I'm used to it.
你厌倦每个周末都于此工作吗
So you ever get tired of working here every weekend?
那你厌烦每个周末都到此吗
Do you ever get tired of coming here every weekend?
伟庭 还不快走
Quentin. You coming or no?
很抱歉 应保持桌面整洁
Sorry. Look, this should take care of the rest of it.
- 再见 - 再见
- See you around. - See you.
或者你应告知其他人
Listen, maybe you should talk to somebody.
我有
I did.
他认为问题发生在之前
And he thinks all my problems come from my past.
我童年那时
We began going through my childhood…
就在那时开始
…and that's when they started.
开始什么
When what started?
诸此恶梦
These nightmares.
恶梦
Nightmares.
你不能入睡
So, what, you can't sleep?
我能入睡
I can sleep.
不过我不想入睡
I just don't want to.
听我说
Okay, Dean, listen to me.
只是梦 不是真的
They're just dreams. Okay? They're not real.
这些梦…
These dreams…
是真实
…they're real.
只是梦
They're not.
不是梦 对不起
They're re… I'm sorry, Kris.
- 好的 - 克莉丝
- No, it's okay. - Kris.
没事 我去整理一下
No, no. It's fine. I'm gonna go clean myself off.
没事
It's okay. It's okay.
只是梦
You're not real.
You're not real. You're not real!
我不是梦
I am now.
阿斌 你在干嘛
Dean, what are you doing?
- 只是梦 - 住手
- You're not real. - Dean, stop it. Dean.
住手
Dean, stop it!
阿斌
Dean!
《新猛鬼街：梦杀》
悲痛震动我们的内心
Tragedy can shake us at our core…
它使我们团结与互勉
…and it can also unite us in our shared grief.
我们在这天共聚
Today we are gathered and united…
为此人的逝去与他生前的痛楚
…for the tragic loss of a young man with so much life ahead of him.
让我们祈祷
Let us pray.
上帝 请将死亡的阴影
Lord, you who can turn the shadow of death…
转化为明亮的新一日
…into the light of a new day…
我们将阿斌托付于你
…as we gather to commend Dean into your hands…
有助我们以忏悔的心仰望你
…help us to wait upon thee with penitent hearts…
警惕我们 他的逝去就是我们的存在
…and remind us of he who died that we might live.
权力和荣耀直到永远 阿门
And the power and the glory forever and ever. Amen.
- 天啊 - 没事了
- Amen. - Come on, sweetie. It's over.
是的
Yeah.
来慰问下
Let's go say hi.
- 歌雯 还好吧 - 阿兰 你好
- Gwen. Hi, how are you? - Alan, hi.
- 好久不见 - 是
- It's been a long time. - Yeah, yeah.
- 尤其在这些情形 - 不过…
- Especially under these circumstances. - Yeah, not a…
南希 若你想找人倾诉
You know, Nance, if you need someone to talk to…
我没事 有劳关心
I'm okay. Thank you.
我们在学校设置了应急中心
We're setting up a crisis center at the school.
- 你知道我办公点吧 - 嗯
- You know where my office is, right, Nancy? - Yeah.
- 我们要离开了 珍重 - 见到你真高兴
- We're gonna head out. Take care. - Good to see you.
再见 伟庭
Bye-bye, Quentin.
你认识阿斌很久了
You knew Dean that far back?
那女孩是我 但不知为何在此照片里
Jesus, that is me. But I don't know how I'm in that picture.
我在高中才认识阿斌
I didn't meet Dean until high school.
走
Come on.
- 阿斌死前若有所言 - 节哀顺变
- Dean said something right before he died. - Oh, please don't.
他说「只是梦」
He said, "You're not real."
重复不止
He kept repeating it over and over again.
知其含义吗
Do you have any idea what that means?
我不知道
No. I don't.
有什么含义 或许他嗑药了
Think about it. What would it mean? Dean was on a load of medication when…
杰西
Jesse.
事发时 如有人在迫他
When it happened, it was like somebody was making him do it…
但根本没人
…but there was nobody there.
杰西 你要相信我
Jesse, you have to believe me.
克莉丝 你受惊过度才有这种想法
Kris, it was late and you were scared. Your mind was just playing tricks on you…
我相信你
I believe you.
你相信
You do?
我经历过…
I've seen…
- 我看见… - 你根本没经历过
- I saw… - You didn't see anything.
你又不是当事人
You weren't right there. Kris was.
她很混乱 让她冷静下
She's already fucked up, so leave her alone.
你根本不知道我经历过什么
You have no idea what I've seen.
回家吧
Let's go home.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hi. - Hi.
妈妈 我在找儿时的照片
Hey, Mom, where are all the photos of me from when I was younger?
- 不在这 - 谁晓得
- They're not here. - Oh, well, who knows?
可能放在车库 怎么了
They're probably packed away over the garage. Why?
今日在葬礼上…
Because today at the funeral I, um…
我看到我和阿斌的儿时合照
I saw a photo of Dean and I when we were, like, 5.
好奇怪 我是在高中才认识阿斌
But, you know, it's funny, I don't remember knowing Dean before high school.
谁能记得五岁时的事
Who can remember being 5 years old?
快收拾好 晚膳已备好
Hey, why don't you pack those up? Dinner's almost ready.
晚安 乖女儿
Good night, honey.
记得我吗
Remember me?
克莉丝 没事吧
Kris? You okay?
那是什么
What is that?
没什么
Uh, nothing.
好像是速写画
Just, like, a sketch.
还好吧
Are you okay?
- 很好 - 是吗
- Yeah, I'm okay. - Yeah?
那你呢
Are you okay?
还用说
Yeah, you know.
若你需要找人谈话
You know, like, if you ever need somebody, if you ever wanna talk to somebody, l…
我猜有一大堆人愿意听
I'm sure you have like a thousand other people you could talk to…
我亦是当中的一份子…
…but if you wanna talk to somebody…
谢谢
Thanks.
伟庭 要迟到了 快走
Quentin. You're gonna be late to class. Come on, buddy, let's go.
- 我爸爸 - 我知道
- My dad. - I know.
正是伯里克利告诉雅典人
Now, class, it was Pericles who told the Athenian people…
他们应聚集到城门
…they should all gather into the gates of the city…
同时他的海军舰队摧毁斯巴达人的航道
…while his naval fleet picked off the Spartans by sea.
现在胜利已在握
Now, it was to be a slow but sure victory.
伯里克利曰“斯巴达人绝不会攻下雅典卫城墙”
The Spartans would never make it over the walls of the acropolis, Pericles said.
但他没料到会被瘟疫打败
But what he didn't take into account is that the plague would eventually strike.
翻到书中八十四页
Open your books to page 84.
情形更复杂
To further complicate matters…
斯巴达人配备了各种各样武器
…the Spartans were armed with a variety of weapons…
当中有些武器是即场组装
…some of them even improvised.
他们不停屠杀雅典人
And they would not hesitate to slaughter every Athenian they saw…
甚至孩童
…even children.
尤其是士兵的小孩…
Especially the children of soldiers. This is where the…
醒醒
Wake up.
Wake up, wake up, wake up.
你上课不该打瞌睡
You really shouldn't fall asleep in class.
- 你好 克莉丝 - 你是谁
- Hi, Kris. - Who are you?
你看起来更甚…
You look just as beautiful…
漂亮
…as ever.
不用担心
You have nothing to worry about.
不痛的
This won't hurt…
…只会有…
…one…
…一点点…
…little…
…痛而已…
…bit.
没事吧 霍士小姐
Are you okay, Miss Fowles?
怎么了
What happened?
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
什么
What?
克莉丝
Kris!
路路
Rufus.
路路 你怎么了
Rufus, what are you doing?
怎么会在屋外
Huh? What are you doing out here?
进来
Come on.
路路
Rufus.
快
Come on.
嗨
Hey.
今晚我要搭夜航班去伦敦
I have to fly to London on a redeye tonight.
好的
Okay.
无恙吧
You gonna be okay?
很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
我安好无恙 一路顺风
I'm gonna be all right. Have a safe flight.
我只是担心你
I just worry about you.
- 要多休息 - 好的
- Try and get some sleep. - Okay.
下机后我会致电你
I'll call you when I land.
我爱你
I love you.
Love you.
杰西
Jesus, Jesse.
- 你在这干嘛 - 快让我进去
- What the hell are you doing here? - Are you gonna let me in?
进来吧
Yeah, come in.
我知我蠢材
All right, I know I've been an asshole…
我爱吃醋兼懵性
…and I've been jealous and I've been fucked up.
但阿斌亦是我朋友
But Dean was my friend too.
麻烦告诉我发生何事
Will you please tell me what's been going on?
我做了个梦
I'm having these dreams.
梦醒仍心有余悸
And I'm scared.
我猜阿斌亦做过
I think Dean was having them too.
克莉丝 听着 我们都…
Kris, listen, we've all…
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
每次发梦时
But now every time I dream…
总会梦见那个男人
…I always see this man.
一个…
And he's…
被烧伤过的男人
He's burned…
他一直试图
…and melted. And he's always trying to…
- 用刀攻击我 - 是他的铁刀手
- attack me with these knives… - Knives on his fingers.
什么
What?
天啊
Oh, my God.
我们都做过相同的梦
We're having the same dream.
- 不可能 - 事实是这样
- Kris, it's not possible. - It is possible.
- 只是梦 对不 - 不只是梦
- It's just a dream, all right? - It's not a dream.
嘘 嘘
Shh. Shh.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
我好怕
I'm so afraid.
我现想入睡 又怕会梦中被杀
All I wanna do is go to sleep, but if I do he's gonna kill me like Dean.
我们别再谈这个
Maybe we should just stop talking about it, all right?
唯恐日有所思夜有所梦
We keep talking about it, we'll keep thinking about it, then we'll keep dreaming about it.
望着我
Look at me.
你会陪着我
You'll stay with me?
我会守护着你
Of course I'll stay with you.
路路
Rufus!
过来
Rufus, get in here!
路路
Rufus!
该死
Ugh. Shit.
路路
Rufus.
Rufus?
过来
Rufus, come here, boy!
Come here.
路…
Ru…
路…路
Ru… Rufus.
噢 我的…
Oh, my…
我在爱护它
I was just petting him.
杰西 救命
Jess! Help!
不 不
No! No!
帮我
Help me, please! Help me!
一 二
One, two
佛莱迪要来抓你了
Freddy's coming for you
- 来吧 来吧 - 三 四 锁好你的门
- Come on. Come on. - Three, four, better lock your door
找藏身之处
We have to hide.
- 五 六 快去拿十字架 - 五…
- Five, six, grab your crucifix - Five…
七 八 彻夜不眠
Seven, eight, gonna stay up late …four…
三
…three…
二
…two…
一
…one.
- 准备好了吗 - 噢 天啊
- Ready or not… - Oh, my God.
我来啦
…here I come.
- 杰西 - 嗯
- Jesse? - Mm.
杰西
Jess?
捉到你
Found you.
克莉丝 没事啦 停啊
Kris! All right… Hey! Hey! Kris, stop!
停手
Kris! Stop! Kris!
天啊
Oh, my God.
醒醒
Wake up!
克莉丝
Kris!
该死
Oh, shit.
克莉丝
Kris?
天啊
Oh, God.
克莉丝
Kris?
该死
Oh, shit.
Fuck.
没事了 好了
Okay, okay.
好了 好了 没事了
Okay, okay, okay.
我已报警了
Hey! Hey, you! I'm calling the cops!
乖女
Honey?
南希
Nancy.
- 南希 - 怎么
- Nancy. - Yeah?
半夜三更 还不去睡
It's the middle of the night. You need to go to sleep, hon.
知道了
Okay, I will.
- 马上 - 好的
- Now. - Okay.
- 南希 是我 - 杰西 发生什么事
- Nancy, it's me. It's me. - Jesse. What the…
- 嘿 嘿 - 你来这干嘛
- Hey, hey. - What are you doing here?
- 听我说 - 发生何事
- Stop. Just listen to me, okay? - What happened to you?
- 你流血了 - 认真听我说
- Whose blood is that? Is it your blood? - Listen, okay? Please.
- 克莉丝她… - 你对她做了什么
- I was with Kris and… - What'd you do to her?
是另有其事
I didn't do anything, I'm trying to tell you. Listen to me, something's going on, okay?
- 克莉丝怎么了 - 有人在梦中杀死克莉丝
- Tell me what happened to Kris, Jesse. - Someone killed her in her sleep.
神么
What?
- 你在说什么 - 别装不知道
- What are you talking about? - Don't pretend you don't know…
你说过你经历过
…because you do. You said it at the funeral.
那个男人一直想在梦中杀死我们
He's the one who's trying to kill us in our dreams.
- 我听过首歌谣 - 歌谣
- All I keep hearing is the song. - What song?
一 二
One, two
佛莱迪为你而来
Freddy's coming for you
佛莱迪
Freddy.
- 那梦魔的名字 - 不可能
- That's his name and he's in all of our heads. - No, that's impossible. No.
南希
Nancy.
我们要制止他
Shit. We gotta stop this.
- 有何计划 - 我不知道
- How? - I don't know.
唯有不入睡
Just don't fall asleep.
若梦死 则身死
If you die in your dreams, you die for real.
南希 有谁在里面
Nancy? Who's in there?
该死
Oh, shit.
警察 不要动
Police. Don't move!
趴下
Get down! Get down!
- 我没犯事 - 下来
- I didn't do anything. - Down!
听着 凶手不是我
Listen to me, I didn't do anything. Please.
- 趴下 - 啊
- Get down! - Aah!
我爱她 岂会杀害她
I loved her, man! I couldn't kill her!
发生什么事
What's going on down there?
我没犯事
I didn't do anything! Stop!
闭嘴
Shut up.
- 起来 - 我没杀她
- Get up. - I didn't kill her! You know!
- 闭嘴 - 捉到个疑犯
- Shut the fuck up. - That's a roger, two-two.
起来
Get up.
- 叫他进来 - 带他离开这里
- Call it in, code four. - Get him out of here.
重复 已捉到凶手
Copy that, we've got a homicide.
凶手已被拘捕
Code four. Homicide suspect in custody.
南希 你深知幕后黑手
Nancy! You know! You know who did it!
进来
Coming in.
打开三号
Open three.
明白
Clear.
消灭四号
Clear four.
- 带他出去 - 好的
- Let him out. - All right.
打开五号
Hold five open.
打开四号
Open four.
- 喂 - 我是南希
- Hello? - Hi, it's Nancy.
嗨
Hey.
你答应过我想的话就可致电你
You said to call you if I needed to talk.
- 嗯 - 克莉丝死了
- Yeah. - Kris is dead.
保持清醒
Stay awake.
- 保持清醒 - 静点
- Stay awake. - Quiet.
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up.
将近$24.97
That'll be $24.97.
五 四 三 二
Five, four, three, two…
五 六 七
Five, six, seven…
做恶梦
Nightmares?
是的
Yeah.
佛莱迪
Freddy?
打开四号
Open four.
起来
Get up.
有人保释你
Folks posted your bail.
杰西 救我
Jesse, help me.
救我啊
Help me, please.
克莉丝
Kris?
- 哦 天啊 - 不
- Oh, God. - No.
是我
Just me.
你想怎样
What do you want from me?
我不知道
Hmm. I don't know, Jesse.
你可以时光倒流
You think you can turn back time?
- 答我 - 不是
- Answer me! - No.
你可以起死回生
Do you think you can bring the dead back to life?
- 不能 - 不能吗
- No. No! - No?
深有同感
I didn't fucking think so.
不 不 不
No! No! No!
你尖叫什么 我还没动手
Why are you screaming? I haven't even cut you yet.
我没杀人 我是无辜
I didn't do it! I'm innocent!
放我出去
Get me out of here!
快放我出去
Let me the fuck out of here!
知不知道心跳停止后
Did you know that after the heart stops beating…
大脑功能仍能运作超过七分钟
…the brain keeps functioning for well over seven minutes?
还有六分钟多的时间可以玩
We got six more minutes to play.
- 还好吧 - 我只是很累
- You okay? - Yeah. I'm just really exhausted.
给
Here.
- 什么玩意 - 振奋剂
- What's that? - Zoneral.
令你保持活力 我十五岁就开始服用
It's basically speed for kids with ADD. I've been on it since I was, like, 15.
不用 有劳关心
No. No. No, thanks.
南希 你没精打采 没事吧
Nancy, look, you're running on fumes. Here, okay? Are you sure? It's…
我没事
Yeah, I'm fine for now.
我不介意你的信仰
I didn't take you for the religious type.
有些东西你得相信
Yeah, well, you gotta believe in something, you know?
这是什么
What's this one doing here?
是本《哈默林的魔笛手》
It's The Pied Piper of Hamelin.
我梦见此书 其讲述一个被城镇背叛的人…
I saw it in one of my dreams. It's about a guy who's betrayed by a town…
向孩童实行报复的事
…and he gets his revenge by taking all their children.
我亦一直梦见到孩童
I keep dreaming about children too.
梦里还有间学校
And then there's also a school.
当中深有含义
Well, it's gotta mean something.
我所指的是 自从六年级我们便没有齐聚上学
Yeah, but, I mean, what? We didn't go to school together until, like, 6th grade.
- 我们在浪费时间 - 什么意思
- Look, we're running out of time. - What do you mean?
恶梦相信是非人为控制而产生
Nightmares are triggered by the belief that the dreamer has no control…
进而引发失眠
…and this can cause insomnia.
若长时处于此状态
But then it says at the 70-hour mark…
失眠者会进入瞌睡状态
…the insomniac will begin to experience micronaps.
人得不到足够睡眠 人便会打瞌睡
"His brain will shut down its functions for seconds in an attempt to recharge."
因此你在梦中 亦以为不是在梦中
This basically means that you're dreaming, but you don't know it.
即使处于清醒状态
Like, even if you're awake.
大脑亦会因疲倦停止运作 导致昏睡
And then it says that after that, your brain will shut down, inducing a coma.
又称深度睡眠
Which is permanent sleep.
南希
Nancy?
Nancy.
什么
Yeah?
嗨
Hey.
你去哪了
Where have you been?
我刚在书店
I was at the bookstore.
我只是想知道你行踪
Okay, well, I didn't know where you were.
我有预感 你朋友会遭遇不测
And I just feel like, with everything that's been happening with your friends…
妈妈
Hey, Mom?
我是否同克莉丝…
Do I have some sort of connection with Kris…
阿斌和杰西及伟庭
…and Dean and Jesse?
有某种关联
Or Quentin?
或者我们小时曾共聚上学
Like, maybe we went to school together when we were little or something like that?
没有这回事
Not that I can recall.
你认识个叫佛莱迪的人吗
Did we ever know a guy named Freddy?
不认识
I don't think so.
好吧
Okay.
晚安
Good night.
我是歌雯
Hey, it's Gwen.
南希开始记起
Nancy's starting to remember.
没事吧
Honey, you okay?
很好
Yeah, I'm fine, Mom.
- 我要入睡了 - 好的
- All right. I'm going to bed. - Okay.
南南
Little Nancy.
长大成人了
All grown up.
你只是梦魇
You're just a nightmare.
没错
That's right.
没人可证明我曾在此
No one can prove I was ever here.
你是谁
Who are you?
你不记得
You don't remember?
你是…
You must.
我最痛爱的
You're my number one.
你是我的…
You're my…
南南
…little Nancy.
我设了闹铃
I set an alarm.
绝对有啦
Yes, you did.
有在梦中设闹钟
In your dream.
你果然与众不同
You smell different.
伟庭
Quentin?
南希 他杀死了杰西
Nancy, he got to him. Jesse's dead.
杰西在梦中猝死
He died in his sleep.
我见过他
I saw him.
- 刚才睡梦中我梦见他 - 好 我过来
- I fell asleep. I saw Freddy. - All right, I'm coming over.
好的
Okay.
该死
Shit.
这是贝瀚幼稚园
So Badham's a preschool.
一间位置偏僻 废置久时的幼稚园
It's on the other end of town. It was closed years ago.
找不到图片
Can't find any pictures.
等等 过来
Wait, come here.
梦醒后我画了这个
I drew this after my dream.
我未曾见过
I don't know. I've never seen it before.
那个人和学校有何联系
How is the guy in our dreams connected to the school?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我知家母略有隐瞒
But I know my mom's hiding something.
不在这
There's nothing here.
帮我
Help me.
那是什么
What is that?
我们都在这
We're all here.
克莉丝 杰西 阿斌
Kris, Jesse, Dean.
我 还有你
It's me, it's you, it's…
你们在干嘛
What are you doing?
南希 发生什么事
Nancy, what is going on?
- 给我照片 - 我不明白
- Give me the picture. - I don't understand.
你说过我们未曾谋面
You said that… You said that we didn't know each other.
但我们都在照片里 我们在同间幼稚园
But we're all in this picture. We went to school together.
给我照片
Give me the picture.
- 够了 - 为何隐瞒
- It's okay. - Why would you lie to me?
- 我没隐瞒 - 证据确凿 为何隐瞒
- I didn't lie. - It's right here. Why would you lie to me?
- 别再隐瞒我 - 我没隐瞒你
- Stop lying. You're lying to me. - I'm not lying to you.
- Stop lying to me! - I am not lying to you!
我不想你带着以往的记忆生活
I didn't want you to have to go through your life with this memory!
我只是想你忘记往事
I didn't want you to remember. I wanted you to forget!
忘记什么
Remember what?
我幼时发什么事
What happened at that preschool?
微笑
Smile, everybody.
精神抖擞
You guys look great.
有个叫佛莱迪·克鲁格
There was a man at the preschool.
出现于校园
His name was Fred Krueger.
一 二
One, two
佛莱迪为你而来
Freddy's coming for you
三 四 锁好你的门
Three, four. Better lock your door
他是个园丁
He was a gardener.
居住于学校地下室
He lived in the basement of the preschool…
而你们取笑他的人生
… and you kids were his life.
四
Four…
三
…three…
二
…two…
一
…one.
我们原先不敢相信
We didn't wanna believe it at first.
准备好没
Ready or not…
你们太天真
You all were so innocent.
我来了
…here I come.
至于你 南希
And you, Nancy…
你在画什么 不错啊
What are you drawing? That is so good.
你是他最得意门生
… you were his favorite of all.
我这里有其他画
You know what? I got some other drawings.
画得不怎样 或许你帮我修改
And they're, like, really bad drawings. Maybe you can help me fix them?
接着我们注意到一些事
And then we started to notice things.
他近来举止有点怪异
Yeah. Uh, he has been acting a little strange lately.
他把我们带到秘密洞穴
He takes us to the secret cave.
没事了
It's okay. It's all right.
跟着你们就报警
So, what did you do? Did you call the police?
当我们要对付他时 他已离开
He left town before we ever were able to confront him.
他离开 不能再伤害你了
He's gone. He can't hurt you anymore.
所以你们都会梦见
So these dreams that you're having…
他们被压抑的记忆
…they're repressed memories…
来于那可怖的时光
…from a terrible, terrible time.
希望你是对的
I hope that you're right.
我们要找出相中其他小孩
We have to find the other kids in the picture.
- 你们在说什么 不行 - 一点意义也没有
- What are you talking about? No. - It doesn't make any sense.
- 必须知己知彼 - 肯定有意义
- There's gotta be more to it. It's not… - This makes total sense.
听你妈妈话 那只是回忆
You heard your mom. These are just memories.
- 若她错了 - 我们仍在经受那般生活…
- What if she's wrong? - We're experiencing them…
- 而你们却说只是回忆 - 你知道什么
- living them, but they're just memories. - How do you know that?
回忆不会杀人的
Memories don't kill you.
- 伟庭 上车 - 是我爸爸 我得走
- Whoa, whoa, whoa! Quentin, get in the car. - It's my dad. I gotta go.
- 我们要采取措施 - 停
- We have to do something. - Look, stop.
太荒谬了
This is crazy. Listen to yourself.
对不起
I'm sorry.
希望你们做四百秒热身运动 二百下的胸压式游泳
I want you to do 400 warm-up. Then do a 200-back-breast drill swim.
伟庭 集中 清醒 进入状态
Quentin, I need you to focus. I need you to wake up, get into this.
继续 好
Let's go. All right, guys.
上去 继续
Step up. Let's go. On the blocks.
打破你记录
Take your mark.
确保你们在水中正常发挥
Make sure you're working your underwaters…
成功转身 进出都十分快
…hit the turns, in and out really quick.
如海豚般有力离开墙面
Powerful dolphins off the wall.
我们要做多次三百秒 下降四次 控制在五至八次
All right, guys, we're gonna do eight 300s, descend one to four, hold five to eight.
离开 我们开始
All right, hop out. On the blocks, guys. Let's go.
加速
Let's step up.
打破你记录
Take your mark.
继续 快点
Come on, pick it up. Let's go. Come on.
开始 不错
Come on. Come on, let's go. Attaboy.
快点
Come on, now. Come on. Come on, let's go.
快
Come on.
Come on!
等等
Wait!
嗨
Hey!
好吧
Okay.
- 佛莱迪 - 出来 你个衰人
- Krueger! - Come on out, you bastard!
快开门
Goddamn it. You open this door, Krueger!
你们想干嘛
What do you think I did?
- 我们不会对你怎样 - 开门 滚出来
- I didn't do anything! - Get your ass out. Open the fucking door!
- 休想我开门 - 阿乐 把守后门
- I didn't do it! - Norm, make sure…
- 他不能从后面出去 - 好的
- …he can't get out the back! - Okay.
停手
Stop!
停下 好的
Stop. Okay.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
你要干嘛 不可以这样做
What are you doing? No, no, no. This isn't the right way.
- 我们可以报警 - 非做不可
- We gotta call the police. - What is the right way?
我们的小孩饱受折磨 一定要以牙还牙
Our kids get on a stand, tell a room of people what happened?
- 我们要报警 - 他说得对
- No, we've got to call the police. - He's right.
- 并非只有此办法 - 今晚来个了断
- This is not the way to do this. - This ends tonight.
好吧 好吧
Okay. Okay.
为我儿子报仇
This is for my son!
出来 克鲁格
Come out, Krueger!
不
No!
没事吧
Are you okay?
去找护士
Go get the nurse.
深呼吸
Breathe, breathe. Come on. Come on, breathe.
- 放松 深呼吸 - 我没事
- Relax and breathe. Come on. Come on. - I'm okay.
昨晚我做了另个恶梦
I had another nightmare last night.
一个穿条纹毛衣的烧伤男人试图杀我
That burned man with the striped sweater, he keeps trying to kill me.
我向不同路段跑 最后到步幼稚园
I ran a different way this time. I ended up in front of a preschool.
醒之前我有机会查探 但感觉匪夷所思
I woke up before I had a chance to explore, but it has to mean something.
这次他追逐我进入幼稚园
He chased me into the preschool this time.
我逃避到地下室
I got away, made it down to the basement.
似乎他有意要我去地下室
But it feels like that's where he wants me to go. Like…
他想我去找什么似的
… he needs me to find something.
我一闭眼就做梦
I'm starting to dream with my eyes open.
我不能分辨梦与实
I can't tell what's real anymore.
我三天没入睡
I haven't slept in three days.
一入睡就会做梦
If I sleep, I dream.
一发梦就会猝死
If I dream, I'm dead.
是否有相同感受之人
Is there anybody else out there that this is happening to?
有人拯救我吗
Can somebody help me?
劳驾
Please?
他们真的死了
They're all dead.
我知佛莱迪发生何遭遇
I know what happened to Freddy.
你杀了佛莱迪
You killed Krueger.
- 你在哪听来的 - 你追赶他
- Where'd you hear that name? - You chased him…
令他陷入绝境并烧死他
…cornered him and burned him to death. You hunted him!
我们没杀他 我们是在保护你们
We did not hunt him. We were protecting you.
- 为什么 - 惩罚他的所为
- From what? - From him. From what he did to you.
- 皆因你们所说 - 那时我们才五岁 年幼不懂
- From what you kids told us he did to you. - We were 5. We would've said anything!
- 为什么不报警 - 你还年少无知
- Why didn't you go to the police? - You were so young.
我们指责他折磨我们
No. God! And the things we said he did…
你们有没有发现那洞穴
The cave. Did you ever find it?
没有
No.
何以定罪于他
How do you know he was guilty?
- 哦 天啊 - 你滥杀无辜
- Oh, my God. - You killed an innocent man.
嗯 嗯
Mm-mm.
每次我经过事发地 往事历历在目
There's not a day that goes by that I don't think about that night, Quentin.
你活该
Good, you deserve at least that.
伟庭 当你长大成人有妻室
Quentin. When you grow up and you have kids…
便能感同为父感受
…I hope you never know the feeling of utterly failing to protect them.
- 别碰我 - 乖仔
- Don't touch… Don't touch me. - Son…
听我说
You listen to me.
所有人都知道佛莱迪·克鲁格是不存在
As far as everyone around here is concerned, Fred Krueger never existed.
伟庭
Quentin.
等一下
Quentin, wait. Wait.
- 什么 - 冷静
- What? - Slow down.
- 停 - 我们害了他
- Stop. - We got him killed.
我们讲大话
Our stories, our lies.
- 若我们能让他住手 - 行吗
- What if we can make him stop? - What if we can?
曼加说过佛莱迪想让他在幼稚园找东西
The preschool. Marcus said that Freddy wanted him to find something.
好
Fine.
南希
Nancy.
出来闲逛吗
Don't you wanna hang out, Nancy?
你怎么了
What are you doing?
我刚见克莉丝被装在尸袋
I just saw Kris in a body bag.
你已经很久没入睡
All right, you've been up for too long.
你有幻觉 我们要快走
You're having micronaps. We gotta go.
我们要去幼稚园
Let's go find the preschool.
来这里干嘛
What are we doing here?
买些药丸
I need more pills.
快
Come on. Come on.
我要这种药
Hi. Um, I'm gonna need a, um, refill on that, please.
没有替换的
On this, you're out of refills.
我得咨询医生
I'm gonna have to call the doctor on this.
我现在等不了
Look, I don't have time to call a doctor. Look…
天啊
Oh, my God.
我十五岁便开始用这药
Look, I've been on this stuff since I was 15.
完全没不良反应
Okay? It's totally fine.
只需装满它 几颗也行
You just go back, you fill it up and… Even just a couple.
- 几颗也行 - 不行 很抱歉
- All I need is a couple. - No. No, I'm sorry.
伟庭
Quentin. Quentin.
- 装满它 - 不行
- Just fill it up. - No.
不 不
No. No.
醒醒
Wake up!
你流血啊
You're bleeding.
发生什么事
Oh, my God. What happened?
坚持
Hang on.
他的毛衣
His sweater.
- 好的 - 他在这
- Okay. - He's here.
你伤得不轻
Man, you're hurt really bad.
快去医院
Let's go to the hospital. Come on.
贝·文生医生请到ICU
Dr. Blake Mason to ICU, please.
乖女
Baby.
发生什么事
Oh, honey, honey, honey, what happened?
谁干的
Who did this to you?
你深知肚明
Look at it, Mom. You know who did it.
You know who did it.
亲爱的
Oh, honey.
我们怎么弄呢
Okay, how we doing?
很快没事
It's gonna be okay.
给你一点镇静剂
I'm gonna give you a little something for the pain.
- 它会让你昏睡 - 没事的
- It'll put you right out. - It's okay.
不要
No, Mom, I don't want it. I don't want it. I don't want it.
- 没事的 - 不 妈妈
- It's okay, it's okay. - No, Mom, no.
- 我不需要 - 可能会有点痛
- I don't want it. Don't let her do it. - This might sting a bit.
- 不 不 - 不 不
- No! No! - No, no.
- 好的 好的 - 不
- Okay. Okay. - No!
- 伟庭在哪 - 我能和你到走廊商量些事吗
- Where's Quentin? - Can I have a word with you in the hall?
别离开我
Don't leave. Don't leave, Mom. Mom.
伟庭在哪
Where's Quentin? I need Quentin.
如今唯一办法就是令媛需注射镇静剂
Your daughter needs to be sedated, but I can't do anything…
- 我需要你首肯 - 我不想她不再受痛苦
- without your authorization. - I just want her to be out of pain.
好 签名
Good. Sign this.
令媛会没事
She'll be fine.
好
Great.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 还好吧 - 嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
- 怎么 - 这是什么
- Yeah? - What is that?
- 肾上腺激素 可以保持清醒 - 怎么得到的
- Adrenaline. Keep us awake. - Where'd you get it?
我在护士的送药车偷的
I stole it off one of the nurse's carts.
你不能吃 你不知它会否有副作用
You can't take that. You have no idea what it's gonna do.
我别无可选 你要吗
You know what? That is kind of the least of my concerns right now. You want some?
不要
No.
哇
Whoa.
没事吧
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah. I'm good.
走
Let's go.
- 有多远 - 快到了
- How much further? - We're almost there.
和我聊天 我怕睡着
Hey, will you talk to me? I'm falling asleep.
聊什么好
Yeah. What do you wanna talk about?
我没主意
I don't know.
你最喜欢什么颜色
What's your favorite color?
蓝色
Blue.
介不介意说说你这几年怎么过的
Look, if you really wanna talk, how come over the last couple years…
每次我约你 你都没赴约
…every time I've invited you out, you've just never shown up?
我不知道你注意到没 我的确不适
I don't know if you've noticed, but I don't exactly fit in.
若我们能活过接下来的二十四小时
Okay, look, if we survive the next 24 hours…
我们就来次真的约会
…then I'll take you out on a real date.
我不肯呢
Well, what if I say no?
那么快就拒绝我
Well, why don't you sleep on it?
- 怎样 - 没事
- You okay? - I'm fine.
来吧
Come on.
我刚才见到他
I saw him. He was right there.
快走
We gotta go. Come on.
就这
This is it.
就这间学校
This is the school.
不
No!
没事吧
Are you okay?
我分不清梦与现实
I don't know what's real anymore.
来吧
Come on.
跟着我
Follow me.
给我打火机
Hey, give me your lighter.
现在我们在这里又能怎样
All right, well, now that we're here, now what?
我都不记得
Because I don't remember any of this.
这是他房间
This must be his room.
他带我们来这里是有原因
Okay, he brought us here for a reason.
这是他房间
This is definitely his room.
伟庭
Quentin.
- 怎么 - 有东西在那后面
- What? - There's something back there.
我之前来过
I've been here before.
若你保密 我带你去个特别地方
If you can keep a secret, I'll take you to a special place.
那些是什么
What are those?
谁的照片
What are those pictures of?
你的照片
They're all of you.
- 让我看 - 不
- Let me see. - No.
不
No.
噢 天哪
Oh, God.
不
No.
我们错了
We were wrong.
他痛恨我们非因我们撒谎
He's not after us because we lied.
而是我们揭发真相
He's after us because we told the truth.
要我们来是为让我们忆起他的所为
He brought us here so we would remember what he did to us.
天哪 该死
God. Fuck!
该死
Fuck.
他想从我们得到什么 他不会停手
What does he want from us? He's never gonna stop.
我知道我们该做什么
I know what we need to do.
快
Come on.
一定有其他方法
There's gotta be another way.
坐以待毙 只能等死
If we just sit here and do nothing, we're gonna die.
- 我来负责 - 我负责扯他毛衣
- I should do this. - I'm the one who pulled his sweater out.
若我是唯一能由梦中带他出来
What if I'm the only one who can bring him out?
我不能让你睡着 不然你就醒不过来
Nancy, I can't let you go to sleep. You're not gonna wake up.
我知道你不会让它发生
I know you won't let that happen.
若你看我在挣扎 就叫醒我
Wake me up if you see me struggle.
希望带给你好运
Gotta believe in something, right?
我会一直陪伴你
I'm gonna be here when you get up.
会成功的
We're gonna make it.
哦 该死
Aw, shit.
你救不了她
You can't save her.
捉到你
Tag.
你好碍眼
You're it.
佛莱迪
Krueger!
你女友来了 我会回来的
Your girlfriend's here. I'll be right back.
一 二
One, two
猜猜谁为你而来
Guess who's coming for you
小南希
Little Nancy.
你找我了 接下玩什么游戏
Now that you caught me, what game do you wanna play next?
- 去你的 - 好像很好玩
- Fuck you. - Ooh. Sounds like fun.
进度是快了点
It's a little fast for me.
吊起来做怎样
How about we hang first?
不是真的
No. It's not real.
是真的
It's real.
我是真的
I'm real.
来个春梦怎么样
Now, how's this for a wet dream?
伟庭 叫醒我
Quentin, wake me up.
这群
This dress…
一直是我心头好
…was always one of my favorites.
还记得吗
Do you remember it, Nancy?
你当然记得
Of course you do.
现在你记得一切
You remember everything now, don't you?
你的记忆刺激了我
Your memories are what fuels me.
不要
No. Please don't.
你真是
Your mouth says no…
口不对心
…but your body says yes.
不要躲开
Don't turn away.
看着我
Look at me!
看我要对你做什么
Look what you did to me.
游戏开始
Now it's time to play.
过瘾吗
Are you having fun?
你好顽皮
Naughty girl.
你伤害不到我的
You can't hurt me.
你所处我的世界
You're in my world.
你离开不了的
And you can't ever leave.
叫声简直引人入胜
That's music to my ears.
我要清醒
I wanna wake up!
你不能醒
You can't wake up.
你已经很久没入睡
I had to keep you awake long enough so when you finally slept…
你绝不会再醒来
…you'd never wake up again.
南希 醒醒
Nancy, wake up.
Wake up, Nancy, wake up!
让我们在这里长相厮守
We're gonna be in here a long time.
- 南希 快醒 - 你认为你男友
- Nancy, please! - Did you really think your boyfriend…
- 可以叫醒你 - 不要
- could wake you up? - Please, don't do this!
求求你
Please!
我是你现任男友
I'm your boyfriend now.
南希 回来 快醒
Nancy, come back! Please, wake up!
你答应过的
You promised!
发个好梦
Sweet dreams.
伟庭 捉住他
Quentin, get him.
你个衰人
Die! Fucking bastard!
雕虫小技
Nice try, Nancy.
现在该我试试
Now let me take a stab.
为什么你还没死
Now, why don't you just fucking die?
很痛吧
It hurts, doesn't it?
那是你现在在现实世界
That's because you're in my world now, bitch.
等等
Wait.
- 给我一些时间 - 瞄高一点
- Give me some slack. - Yeah, aim it up a little higher.
没有任何身体的迹象
No sign of a body anywhere.
好 伟庭
Hey, Quentin.
恶梦完了
Nightmare's over.
你快去休息
I want you to go straight up to bed, okay?
好的
Yeah.
嗨 妈妈
Hey, Mom?
我知道你只想保护我 谢谢
I know you were just trying to protect me. Thank you.
你没事就好
I'm just glad you're safe.